



120 13th Avenue, Apt 212 Minneapolis, MN 55413



(651) 399-3097



mrsbrookekumar@gmail.com



**Brooke Kumar LinkedIn** 

# **OBJECTIVE**

Experienced Program Analyst and Manager successful at cross- functional collaboration and project execution. Specializing in empowering others through dedicated consistency and delivery with an emphasis on buy-in and trust building. Self-motivated professional with proven results excited about career growth.



# **BROOKE KUMAR**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**PD Program Management Specialist, Medtronic** 

12/2017-Present • EU MDR CRHF/AFS Core Team Consulted for Planet Pharma, converted to full-time August 2018.

**Business Analyst, Abbott** 

04/2017-12/2017 • EU MDR Corporate Core Team Consulted for Experis US.

Regulatory Affairs Specialist, DaVita Clinical Research

02/2016-02/2017 ● Regulatory Affairs
Consulted for Robert Half, converted to full-time August 2016.

I have a passion for leveraging Program Management fundamentals to lead functional teams to success from planning to execution. I also have experience implementing a variety of tools to execute projects.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN

Certificate, Full Stack Coding Anticipated March 2020

Carthage College, Kenosha, WI

BA, Religious Studies, *cum laude* Outstanding Senior Thesis, Humanities Department May 2014

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Intermediate Excel, Microsoft 2016

## **IN-PROGRESS CERTIFICATIONS**

- PMP (anticipated Fall 2019)
- Full Stack Coding (anticipated March 2020)

# **SKILLS**

Microsoft Suite • PMP (Microsoft) • Report analysis • Project planning • Advanced MS Project • Gap assessment • Presenting to large groups (50+) • Advanced data visualization • Spotfire • Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS, API integration) • Stakeholder success • Cross-functional collaboration • Project monitoring